Gyuhyeon Hwang

Software developer

Senior student software developer specializing in Python/Django server development. Familiar with collaboration through the internship and team project experience with Git and Notion. Use Python and C++ as primary languages and usually participated in data analysis and web development project.

Contact

Email:

hwgyuhyeon@gmail.com

Portfolio:

hgyuhyeon.github.io

Education

Department of Computer Science – Chungbuk National University

Bachelor of Science 2019.03 – 2024.02(Expected)

Computer Science – Angelo State University

Study Abroad 2022.01 – 2022.05

Languages

English – B2

Korean - Native

Japanese – A2

Skill

- Python, C++
- MySQL, SQLite
- Git, Notion

- Django, DRF
 - RESTful API

Experience

Software Developer (Internship), 2022.06 – 2022.07

Headstart SV, Seoul, South Korea (Hybrid)

- Work as a Django server developer.
- Experience with all stages of the development cycle.
- Work with 7 members by communicating with Notion and Slack.
- Manage and finalize the team project.

Web Developer, 2021.06 – 2021.07

Flug Mediaworks, Cheongju, South Korea

- Implement a web page including PHP/JavaScript backend and HTML/CSS frontend based on a designed draft.
- Translate the Korean website to English and apply it to the English version with a session.

Project

Software Developer, 2022.06 – 2022.07

Recommade, Headstart SV internship program

- A website that recommends music according to the atmosphere of the photo.
- Work as a server developer with 2 of server developer members.
- Design structure of the Django server and implement GET playlists and GET one playlist API under RESTful rules.
- Apply the AI model and React web project to the Django server.
- Connect Django, MySQL, Nginx, and React via docker-compose and deploy to AWS EC2.